alltopics.com 2017-08-08

# : Most Popular News, Videos and Images

### Introduction

Topday.com takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously.

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by Automattic (WordPress.com), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Topday.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Topday.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Topday.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Topday.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Topday.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Topday.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Topday.com’s websites choose to interact with Topday.com in ways that require Topday.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Topday.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Topday.com.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Topday.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Topday.com. Topday.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Topday.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Topday.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Topday.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Topday.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Topday.com ’s behalf or to provide services available at Topday.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Topday.com’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Topday.com or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Topday.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Topday.com may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, Topday.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Topday.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Topday.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Topday.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Topday.com website and have supplied your email address, Topday.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Topday.com and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Topday.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

You should also be aware that if you submit information to “chat rooms,” “forums” or “message boards” such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.

### Cookies

Topday.com places a cookie on the hard drive of your computer. A "cookie" is a file which allows us to track and target the interests of users. In addition, our website uses third party cookies from Google Analytics for Display Advertisers, including the following features:

• Google Display Network Impression Reporting - which gives us additional insight into who has viewed our paid digital advertising on other websites. This will help us optimise and tailor our advertising.

• DoubleClick Platform integrations & Remarketing with Google Analytics – the integrations between both our web analytics and paid advertising platforms together to give us additional insight. This allows us to tailor our advertising to ensure the right types and offers are shown to you while you are using the internet outside our website.

• Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting - which gives us insight into behaviour information relating to visitor age, gender and interests on an anonymous and aggregate level. This will help us to understand browsing behaviour to give you a better experience whilst visiting our sites.

Cookies are used to analyse your use of our website and to serve ads when you visit our website. The information we collect and share with third parties through cookies is aggregated and therefore anonymous (it does not include personal information which is likely to identify you). The information may be used to serve you ads in relation to our products when you visit our website and third party websites. You can access information about Google's Privacy Policy here. While we recommend that users enable cookies on their browsers in order to enjoy all the features of our website, the decision remains in the hands of the individual.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any Topday.com websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Topday.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by Topday.com. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Topday.com does not own or control, or employees that Topday.com does not manage. Topday.com website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and Topday.com and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

### Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

### Choice/Opt-out

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Topday.com may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Topday.com’s sole discretion. Topday.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
